<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ScrollView xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    android:layout_width="fill_parent"
    android:layout_height="fill_parent"
    android:background="@color/background"
    android:padding="8.0dip"
    android:scrollbars="none">

    <LinearLayout
        android:layout_width="wrap_content"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:orientation="vertical">

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="fill_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:background="@drawable/heading_back"
            android:gravity="center"
            android:text="C++ Programming Lab"
            android:textColor="#ffffffff"
            android:textSize="32.0dip"
            android:textStyle="bold" />

        <LinearLayout
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:layout_marginTop="20.0dip"
            android:background="@drawable/chap_heading"
            android:gravity="center"
            android:orientation="vertical">

            <TextView
                android:layout_width="fill_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:layout_marginTop="10.0dip"
                android:gravity="left"
                android:text="List of Programs as Assignments"
                android:textColor="#ff2b1e1e"
                android:textSize="25.0dip"
                android:textStyle="bold" />

            <TextView
                android:layout_width="wrap_content"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:layout_gravity="center"
                android:layout_marginTop="20.0dip"
                android:layout_marginBottom="10.0dip"
                android:gravity="left"
                android:padding="5.0dip"
                android:text="1.Write a Program to design a class having static member function named showcount() which has the property of displaying the number of objects created of the class. \n\n2. Write a Program which creates &amp; uses array of object of a class.( for eg. implementing the list of Managers of a Company having details such as Name, Age, etc..). \n\n3. Write a Program to swap private data members of classes named as class_1, class_2 using friend function. \n\n4.Write an inline function to find largest of three number. \n\n5. Write a Program using copy constructor to copy data of an object to another object. \n\n6. Write a program to perform addition of two complex numbers using constructor overloading. The first constructor which takes no argument is used to create objects which are not initialized, second which takes one argument is used to initialize real and imag parts to equal values and third which takes two argument is used to initialized real and imag to two different values. \n\n7. Write a program for overloading operator++ and operator—using friend functions. \n\n8. Write a program for developing a matrix class which can handle integer matrices of different dimensions. Also overload the operator for addition, multiplication &amp; comparison of matrices. \n\n9.Writea C++ program to compute area of right angle triangle, equilateral triangle, isosceles triangle using function overloading concept. \n\n10.Write a Program to design a student class representing student roll no. and a test class (derived class of student) representing the scores of the student in various subjects and sports class representing the score in sports. The sports and test class should be inherited by a result class having the functionality to add the scores and display the final result for a student. \n\n11.Write a Program illustrating how the constructors are implemented and the order in which they are called when the classes are inherited. Use three classes named alpha, beta, gamma such that alpha, beta are base class and gamma is derived class inheriting alpha &amp; beta. \n\n12. Write a program to raise an exception if any attempt is made to refer to an element whose index is beyond the array size. \n\n13.Write a program to read the class object of student info such as name , age ,sex ,height and weight from the keyboard and to store them on a specified file using read() and write() functions. Again the same file is opened for reading and displaying the contents of the file on the screen. \n\n14.Write a program to perform the deletion of white spaces such as horizontal tab, vertical tab, space ,linefeed ,new line and carriage return from a text file and store the contents of the file without the white spaces on another file."
                android:textColor="#ff2b1e1e"
                android:textSize="20.0dip"
                android:textStyle="italic" />
        </LinearLayout>

        <LinearLayout
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:layout_marginTop="10.0dip"
            android:background="@drawable/chap_heading"
            android:gravity="center"
            android:orientation="vertical">

            <TextView
                android:layout_width="fill_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:layout_marginTop="20.0dip"
                android:text="Text Books:"
                android:textColor="#ff2b1e1e"
                android:textSize="25.0dip"
                android:textStyle="bold" />

            <TextView
                android:layout_width="fill_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:layout_marginTop="10.0dip"
                android:padding="5.0dip"
                android:text="1. J.P.Cohoon&amp;J.W.Davidson- C++ Program Design: An Introduction to Programming and Object-Oriented Design, 2ndEdn, TMH Edn, New Delhi-2000."
                android:textColor="#ff3a2929"
                android:textSize="20.0dip" />

            <TextView
                android:layout_width="fill_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:layout_marginTop="20.0dip"
                android:text="Reference Books:"
                android:textColor="#ff2b1e1e"
                android:textSize="25.0dip"
                android:textStyle="bold" />

            <TextView
                android:layout_width="fill_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:layout_marginTop="10.0dip"
                android:layout_marginBottom="10.0dip"
                android:padding="5.0dip"
                android:text="1. F.L.Friedman&amp;E.B.Koffman- Problem Solving, Abstraction, and Design Using C++,4thEdn, Pearson Education, Inc. 2004."
                android:textColor="#ff3a2929"
                android:textSize="20.0dip" />
        </LinearLayout>
    </LinearLayout>
</ScrollView>